[Music]
oh God I'm going to ask you one more
time what's the name of your tour it's
called the Manchild tour man I told you
already come on I got a wife and kids
hey shut up and answer the questions and
where can I get your special direct.
cc.com
I swear to God I want to uncut and
sensor where could I get that fine you
can download it direct at the website
for five bucks I'll give you the money
man just say I travel light I don't care
a computer with me I carry a tablet and
a phone how can I watch it on there okay
you can download it wherever whenever
you want an unlimited amount of times
it's at your disposal oh God these
answers are giving me it's run around is
it what no all right all right all right
no no no let's talk about this man
Stephen when can I get the special on
iTunes Spotify and Amazon I'd really
love to watch it November 19th it'll be
available on all those places and this
Manchild two of yours where one are you
playing oh no no that's not a good idea
you're not the kind of audience member
that I'm looking for oh really no
no okay okay all right fine fine
fine I'll be in Tempe Tempe Arizona on
December 12th of the 14th okay this love
this time of year where else it is it is
it's beautiful and and I'll be in New
York City New York at Carolines on
December 19th through the 20
[Music]
second okay okay okay okay and Boston ah
Wick it smart e I'll be at the Wilbur on
February 28th it's going to be awesome
Wicked awesome three stops three stops
you call three stops a tour what
where
[Music]
else there's more stops you can find
them all at cc.com
Manchild
is that
good yeah all right man oh that was
great what oh good job man that's a wrap
everybody a rrap excellent work Steve
excellent work what do you mean a rrap a
WAP on what oh hey I'm Bob from uh the
promo
Department what are you talking about
rap what is this great job man we had to
shoot your promo for your special you
guys kidnapped me from a family vacation
kept me down here trapped like an animal
for two weeks yeah we had to put you in
the right place we got gold though for a
promo you guys are you guys
hurt me really bad just say the safe
word if I went too far what safe word
Manchild I said it like 30
times oh yeah all throughout the whole
thing I was saying it you did say it you
did say it you did oh my bad on that oh
yeah oh we should have gotten a
different save
word